glasgow2014.com 2016-11-11

# Privacy | Glasgow 2014 - Commonwealth Games

### Introduction

We are committed to protecting the privacy and security of the information you submit to us.

This Privacy Policy sets out the measures taken by us, Glasgow 2014 Limited (or “ **Glasgow 2014** ”) to protect your privacy when you use our website at [www.glasgow2014.com](http://www.glasgow2014.com/) and any other domains, microsites or webpages maintained by or on behalf of us (in this Privacy Policy, we refer to these sites as “ **the Website** ”).

We describe below the way in which we collect and use your private information and personal data. In this Privacy Policy we refer to your private information and personal data as your “information”.

By using the Website (and submitting your information to us), you agree to our use of your information for the purposes described below. **If you do not agree with any part of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Website or submit any of your information to us**.

### What information do we collect from you and how do we collect it?

When you visit the Website, our web servers automatically collect certain data that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website, such as your IP address and information relating to which pages have been viewed.

Please read the section headed **Cookies** below for information on how we use cookies to collect and use your information.

When you use the Website, we also collect information that you provide to us voluntarily, for example when you complete an online or offline registration form or user survey. The type of information we typically collect includes your name, email address, age and post code.

Sometimes in the course of using the Website, you may choose to upload or post content or information (for example photographs) on public areas of our Website that anyone can see. This sort of content or information is not considered as information that is subject to this Privacy Policy.

### How do we use your information?

The ways in which we use your information depend on the type of information you provide and the purpose for which you provide it. This section sets out different ways we may use your information.

  * If you register for MY2014 email updates on the Website, we may use your information to send you online and / or email communications containing updates on Games progress and developments. If at registration you choose to be alerted about specific topics, we may use your information to send you online and / or email communications related to these topics.
  * We may provide your information to any third party that manages any facility, service or promotion via the Website on our behalf. This includes, for example, any website hosting company or ticketing agent.
  * If you use our “Email a Friend” function, the recipient will receive an email from the address which you entered in "Your email address" and a URL linking to [http://www.glasgow2014.com](http://www.glasgow2014.com/). We will not retain the information you provide.
  * If you submit an online job application via the Website, we may use the information provided by you for the purpose of considering your application. If you are not successful in your application, we may ask you if you are happy for us to keep your information so that we can consider you for future job opportunities.
  * If you register at our procurement portal -<https://businessopportunities.glasgow2014.com/> \- we may use the information provided by you to contact you about Glasgow 2014 business opportunities and to manage the procurement process.
  * We may integrate your personal data from our various databases (for example where you register for different services or updates across our Website) to form a single view of you. This allows us to have an effective and efficient communication with you.
  * We may use your information to compile statistics to help us understand how people use the Website and to customise the Website’s content, lay-out and services. This will allow us to improve the experience on our Website.
  * We may transfer your information and store it at a destination outside the European Economic Area (EEA) for processing by staff operating outside the EEA who work for or are contracted by us, a contractor or another Commonwealth Games organisation. By providing your information to us, you agree to your information being transferred, stored and processed in this way.
  * We may transfer your information if there is a transfer of ownership of the Website or of Glasgow 2014.
  * Only where you have specifically consented for us to do so, we will pass your information onto certain third parties so that they can provide you with relevant information about their products and / or services or for other purposes to which you have consented.

Apart from the purposes described above, we shall only use the information that you provide to us for the purpose described at the point of collection or for purposes that are otherwise legally permitted.

### When are we required to disclose your information?

As noted above, we shall only use the information that you have provided to us for certain defined purposes.

However, we may also disclose your information if we reasonably believe that we are required to do so by law, regulation, court order or any competent governmental, statutory or public body or to protect our rights and property or the rights and property of our partners, licensors or the public.

From time to time, we may also cooperate with a law enforcement agency in any official investigation, and we may disclose your information to that agency in doing so.

### Data Protection

We shall collect, store and use your information in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998.

**Security of your information**

Once we have received information from you, we shall endeavour to protect it by using physical, managerial and technical procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access to it.

We cannot, however, guarantee the security of any information you provide to us in an email or in online form while it is being transmitted to us, because the internet is a potentially unsecure method of information. Any transfer of information from you to us is at your own risk.

Whenever you voluntarily post private information in public areas of the Website, you should be aware that such information can be accessed by the public and may in return be used by others to send you unsolicited communications. We recommend that you exercise discretion in deciding what information you post in public areas of the Website.

**Accuracy of your information**

We shall endeavour to keep your personal data accurate and up-to-date and for no longer than is necessary.

**Your right to access your information held by us**

The Data Protection Act 1998 gives individuals a right of access to their information held by an individual or organisation.

If you wish to access any of your information that we hold, you may make a request in writing using our Subject Access Request Form or by emailing or writing to our Data Protection Manager, whose contact details are set out below. Although the Data Protection Act only requires a request to be in writing (e.g. email, letter), it is helpful for both you and us if you complete the Subject Access Request Form. This allows us to know exactly what information you require without having to contact you to seek clarification, thereby speeding up the process.

Please note that a small fee of £10 is payable to contribute to the cost of looking for your information.

The contact details for our Data Protection Manager are:

Data Protection Manager  
Glasgow 2014 Limited  
Commonwealth House  
32 Albion Street  
Glasgow G1 1LH  
Email: [dataprotection@glasgow2014.com](mailto:dataprotection@glasgow2014.com)

Please contact the Data Protection Manager if you need any guidance concerning a request.

**Managing your information or opting out**

We provide the following options for managing your information and / or removing your information from our database:

1\. Email us at [dataprotection@glasgow2014.com](mailto:dataprotection@glasgow2014.com). Be sure to include your name and clear instructions on what you would like us to do (e.g. update your information or remove your information from our database).

2\. Write to: Data Protection Manager, Glasgow 2014 Limited, Commonwealth House, 32 Albion Street, Glasgow G1 1LH. Be sure to include your name and clear instructions on what you would like us to do (e.g. update your information or remove your information from our database).

3\. Follow the ‘unsubscribe’ link in electronic communications in order to stop receiving such communications from us.

### Cookies

Like most websites, the Website uses cookies. To ensure that we give you the best possible experience on the Website, simple text files called cookies are used which sit on your computer. These cookies will never contain any sensitive information. They are used only by Glasgow 2014 or the trusted partners with whom we work.

By using the Website, you agree to our use of cookies as described below.

What are cookies?

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or alerts you when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. Web applications tailor their operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are most being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve the Website by tailoring it to user needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes, then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better online experience, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the Website. See below for further details of the cookies used by the Website.

**'First Party' cookies (cookies set by the Website itself):**

  * **Microsoft.net Session (ASP.NET_Sessionid)**

This cookie is essential for the Website to function properly. It lasts only for the length of time during which you view the Website, and improves your experience by letting the Website remember things as you move between pages. For example, if you are logged into the Website on one page, this fact is held in your session and you continue to be logged in when you view a different page.

  * **Google Analytics**

__utma  
__utmb  
__utmc  
__utmz

This service monitors how many people are using our Website and which pages are being viewed. This information is stored anonymously, but the cookies help with knowing when the same person returns to view the Website again later. Reports compiled from this information helps us to improve the Website and services.

**'Third Party' Cookies (cookies set by third party websites):**

**Addthis.com** : Cookies are used by the AddThis widget which appears on the Website. More information is available at <http://www.addthis.com/privacy>

**Adjug.com** : Cookies are used by Adjug for tracking users and targeting display of advertising. More information is available at <http://adjug.com/info/privacy.asp>

**Adnxs.com** : Cookies are used by AppNexus advertising for tracking. More information is available at <http://www.appnexus.com/cookies>

**Flickr/ Yahoo!** : Cookies are used by Flickr’s widget embed code and can be attributed to both Flickr and Yahoo! (which owns Flickr). More information is available at <http://info.yahoo.com/privacy/uk/yahoo/cookies>

**Go.affect.tv** : Cookies are used by Affectv for analytics purposes. More information is available at <http://affectv.co.uk/privacy_policy.php>

**Amris.com** : Cookies are used by the system which powers job vacancies and application functionality on the Website.

**Media6degrees.com** : Cookies are used by Media6Degrees for tracking. Media6 Degrees is an analytics company which is part of a network of sites for AddThis. More information is available at <http://m6d.com/info/privacy-policy>

**Pixel.rubiconproject.com** : These cookies are used by RubiconProject to target advertising across sites. More information is available at <http://rubiconproject.com/privacy-policy>

**Managing cookies**

Internet browsers allow you to manage cookies. Devices can be set to accept all cookies, to let you know when a cookie has been allowed or to block cookies.

Each browser works in a different way: use the ‘Help’ menu in your browser to find out how to change your cookie preferences. For information on how to do this on the browser of your mobile phone, you should refer to your handset manual.

Please be aware that disabling cookies completely means that certain personalised features will not be provided, and you may not therefore be able to make full use of all features of the Website.

Some cookies are not set by the Website, but by other sites which provide a service or functionality on our Website. As described above, these ‘third party’ cookies may require you to visit the websites of these third parties to manage, delete or block them.

You can learn more about cookies and how to manage them at [http://aboutcookies.org](http://aboutcookies.org/)

### Other websites

The Website may contain links to other websites which are outside our control and are not covered by this Privacy Policy.

If you access other websites using the links provided, the operators of those websites may collect information from you which will be used by them in accordance with any privacy policy that they may operate, which may be different to our Privacy Policy.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

This is Version 2.0 of our Privacy Policy updated on the 25.02.2013. If this Privacy Policy changes in any way, we will place an updated version on this page. Your continued use of the Website indicates your agreement to any changes.

### How to contact us

We welcome your views about the Website and this Privacy Policy. If you would like to contact us with queries or comments, please send an email to [contactus@glasgow2014.com](mailto:contactus@glasgow2014.com).
